http://www.24-7pressrelease.com/privacy_policy

Pricing & Press Distribution
Why Choose Us?
Where Does Your News Go?
Pricing & Press Distribution
Why Choose Us?
Where Does Your News Go?
Privacy Policy & Cookie Policy
24-7 Press Release Newswire takes privacy seriously. As a leading press release distribution service, we are committed to establishing and maintaining policies and procedures which protect the privacy of personal information gathered from our customers, prospects and other visitors to our website.
24-7 Press Release Newswire is a newswire service which distributes press releases on behalf of our clients. If you submit a press release for distribution through our system, your press release will be transmitted in its entirety. This will include any personal information that is contained in your media contact information. When you submit your press release through our system you agree with our policy and understand that your contact information will be disseminated.
This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by 24-7 Press Release Newswire.
Sharing of Information
24-7 Press Release Newswire not share our users' information with third parties. The only time information is shared is when a customer of 24-7 Press Release Newswire submits their contact information during distribution of their news release.
The information obtained at the time you register with our system is used to keep you up to date of our services and website. It is necessary to register an account with us to track your press releases and make future modifications or enhancements to your release. By having an account with us, you will also have the ability to delete previous press releases from our database that may be out of date or not longer applicable. The information you provide is not shared with outside organizations. This information is kept confidential. Aside from what you make available as contact information in your release, we will not make this information available to any third party. The only time that information submitted may be given out would be in the event of an investigation by authorities, into the company in question. The only information collected is that information which is standard contact information for your press release.
Cookies & Cookies Policy
Our website requires the use of cookies. You may not experience the full functionality of the website if your cookies are turned off.
Personal information you provide to us
If you’re a registered user with 24-7 Press Release Newswire, (including http://mediadesk.24-7pressrelease.com)
We do receive personal information about you (including your name, company, title, e-mail address information, telephone information, beat of interest (for media desk users) combined with categories of interest when you register with us as a registered user.
We may, from time to time collect telephone number information when you call into our customer service desk only to be able to contact you back if we get disconnected, or are unable to take the call at that immediate time. The processing of your information is necessary to process your registration and send services and information you request (such as your subscribed press releases, news feeds and newsletter information) and to answer your questions, inquiries or complaints.
Please note if we do not hold your personal information then we will not be able to provide our services to you.
The information you provided to us will also be used for providing you newsletter and marketing information only upon your consent. This may include beneficial update information for our members.
If you are not a member
On our website, you might complete our contact form, or request information or submit an application to pull our news feeds (including real-time content) or apply for our Agency Preferred discount program. We will need your name, phone number and email address to enable us to respond to your question or application.
If you are just browsing our website we will not collect personal data, unless you consent to a cookie being set. If you accept cookies, we will collect your IP address for various reasons including, to track your usage of the website, recognize you if you return and to make suggestions of other articles or services that we think will interest you, based on your viewing.
What steps do you take for the security of my information?
Our website and business use industry-standard security measures to protect customer data against loss, misuse and interception by third parties.
Periodically, we review and enhance our security policies as necessary.
Dragstrip Designs Marketing Inc., DBA 24-7 Press Release Newswire does not assume any liability for the interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet.
How else can I protect my privacy online?
Generally speaking, whenever you disclose personal information online there is a risk that the information may be intercepted, collected and used. That goes for information disclosed on message boards, in chat areas – or even in e-mail. Dragstrip Designs Marketing Inc. is not responsible if that information is intercepted. You transmit information at your own risk.
Co-branded websites and third party websites and services may be accessible through Dragstrip Designs Marketing Inc. Third parties may collect information for their own contests or promotions, and may have their own privacy and data collection practices. Dragstrip Designs Marketing Inc. is not responsible for and bears no liability for these policies or actions.
You alone are responsible for keeping passwords and information safe. Be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.
Are there other ways my information will be used?
Dragstrip Designs Marketing Inc. may also use or disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under circumstances specifically described to you when we collect the information (such as in a Terms of Service or Use agreement).
IP Address
24-7 Press Release Newswire does track IP addresses, for security reasons only.
Third-Party Sites
24-7 Press Release Newswire contains links to other websites. 24-7 Press Release Newswire is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. You will need to check the policy statement of other websites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.
Security
24-7 Press Release Newswire uses the services of 2Checkout, Paypal, and Authorize.net for secure transactions. These companies use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving user data. 24-7 Press Release Newswire and parent company Dragstrip Designs Marketing Inc. will not be liable for any mishaps that may occur. We do not store credit card information in our systems. Personal information collected at the time of registration is stored in a secure database only accessible by an administrator.
Changes to Privacy Statement
From time to time, we may make changes to this privacy policy. To keep up to date with 24-7 Press Release Newswire's policy, please check this page periodically.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, you may contact us by sending us an email.
